tagadab.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Dedicated and VPS Specialists

Tagadab Ltd adheres to the strictest practises when dealing with our customers personal data. We are fully committed to the protection of your personal data and as such, administer the requirements of the UK's data legislation to the highest standards. So why do we need to keep personal data on our customers? The below explains what we do and why to set your mind at ease:

### 1\. Ordering our products:

To process your order we need to know information about you and/or your company to provision and fulfil your order quickly and effectively. This information will include, but not be restricted to, your name, address, contact details and billing details. You will have the option to opt out of any information that is not required for the order to be processed and we will not collect any data from you without you providing it. Your online customer interface will allow you to update and edit this information as you see fit.

### 2\. Service updates from Tagadab:

By using our service you agree to us using the information we hold on you to provide you with service updates and new products or services that may be of interest to you.

### 3\. Storing and disclosing:

Except for the need to validate your credit or debit card details during these transactions; will never sell, lease or swap your information with any third party for commercial reasons.

Tagadab may pass on your contact details:  

  * to the Police or other competent authority only if it is required to do so by law.
  * to a third party software vendor only if you purchase or rent software licenses from that vendor through Tagadab.

### 4. Third Party Analytics

We have engaged Inspectlet to analyse the activities of visitors to this website, and Inspectlet’s authorized use of cookies and other tracking technologies enable it to have access to Personal Information of visitors to this website. Such access to and use of Personal Information by Inspectlet is governed by Inspectlet’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.inspectlet.com/legal#privacy "Inspectlet legal information").

### 5\. Questions:

Please direct all questions to [support@tagadab.com](mailto:support@tagadab.com "E-mail our support team")
